next picture
[music]
this is a
useful tool for taking things apart and
putting them back together, it
saves you a lot of time
if you
know how to use it, and
recently I bought one
equipped for
exercise, and
I basically just
fill my house with
different things, but I use it.
If you have it, it will take you a few
minutes to assemble around the
house,
repair, or assemble some things,
and if you don't have it, then it can take hours of
exercise. My wife, Vera, isn't so funny. It does this, but she does
n't know how to use it, and
sometimes it's wonderful to find out that yours is
ours, someone doesn't know if they're
married, and whoever is married here knows,
cool, and then you show it, look, this is how you
can use it, so look, here and here,
and now this is
her friend too,
if you know how to use it, how to
use it, this is the best thing.
I had something, my brother,
his
interior was in order, randomly,
once he was driving on the highway,
and
who brought what was there, a thousand-dollar
vehicle that
wasn't repaired, just like you tied
something up there, and in general, the best thing is that
this company is the best
thing since it was, it depends on sex.  And
this
tool, this is also the best, it's the same
best since
sex was invented,
why did he decide to talk about this, the
classic darma
that we actually do, the things we
study, for example, Yandex, we study the
main themes of Buddhism, it's like this
port key with an
internal Allen key,
this tool
[music]
dialogue was this is the
largest
company, so you work there in terms of personnel,
one and a half million, oh, this is worthy of respect,
why am I talking about this,
these guys, we are using schools, only this, and
we take the ancient school on incredibly
deep and powerful, just like this
wrench, and
maybe you can learn which they used,
then you can manage the largest insurance
company in the world,
but this is not
for the average user,
schools only, this is not for the average
user
[music]
no one with him, it means bad days,
we had this before, it
means that some kind of while the cabinet below the
cups are
historical, my, we live in bad times,
people do not respect these teachings, but they
like them more and allowed themselves to kill themselves with food or
buy
expensive cars, and that is, they do not appreciate
wisdom these days
100  Dollars,
what am I, a
drone, no, no
money, it won't be
close,
it doesn't know
the format for workers, that while
now
people don't know, they don't see how to apply this
in real life. You have these
incredibly powerful ancient teachings, very
powerful, a
whole library of Gene Brody, more than 10,000
digitizers, digitized now, an alien,
scanned, people don't know how to
use it, it's just left to
know how to use it.
If they knew, hundreds of thousands and every
week, dollars could be healthy, no, if
you know how, but it's like this egg
wrench,
so
what should he do? Add onion. John
says that a little with pizza. I saw
Jonga.
This is an ancient classic. It makes it
accessible for use by the general
public.
That is, it makes a professional
wrench accessible for use by the
average user.
That is, these ancient teachings with spices
and salt on his John Gamma do not become
digestible to ordinary people. These great
classics are like a school. Only if you
just add a little
experience and
compassion there, they
will suddenly open up and reveal
their secrets to you. That is, this is a wrench.  and
these instructions from him
that these instructions are so difficult but it is
better for him to show how to use them a
wrench and
if you are in it you will not be overcome by
small
tragedies
for example
in 3 3 suddenly comes in this bad season
right after itself but it happened
for example a
peacock and the farms of these peacocks and my viewer
the Internet seemed and found that he was
next to this company when I try to
imitate they began to shout at
I think that for example it could be this
poison
digestion in it is bad
so they
they began to shout
1000 here are these
small liquid ones
marching
enemies of tragedy
for example the
shower broke
if you have a little
special his jong
then a small problem will not knock you
out of the saddle and
then you will go out well everything is fine I
can handle it and
then where in the hope put on such a
trick on a liter and they
say oh do you hear from this jan po
such a cool if you sculpt with spices
other deep teachings this already for us
only everything will help you
practice especially when
some  Troubles happen to you,
you won't lose your practice, then don't
go crazy.
If you have a jong in retreat, you didn't
sit down.
For example, I think the
coolest thing
in India is that if you
wake up, there
are
insects that
drank your blood all night long. Bedbugs like those
that then
sit on the walls, so happy, and
John grew up. Who will you be then, and you'll be
happy about it.
Choose my blood, after all, and as much as you want,
I'll take everything you've lost. You've got all the
winnings. I have enough blood. You
can also drink a little if you
have at least a little. This is also practice, John. Then don't
go crazy when something
unpleasant happens to you in retreat. And
measure
in the text when comments traditionally
also means a relationship of
praise.
Traditionally, before each great
classic of Buddhism, you
bow to someone beautiful, something cool.
For example, I bow to someone
once, and to us, the
almonds of Necrosis. We're just fantasizing.
Now you choose something very
beautiful. Traditionally, before each
great book, it's to bow.
One of the kings of Tibet said, "
We'll organize this worship for someone or something afterward. But
if a book about wine should bow to
the lord gods,
if you and a book about love should be kept, there will be a
garden
for the one you bow to. It's difficult for
people to determine the book's main theme. It
means Chicago has great
compassion. It's surprising that she has a
person, fathers, he's on you. You're leaning towards a
person. UN,
UN, planets, great compassion. And
there's a precedent. Someone else has
already done this before. We'll
talk about this. How I lean silicone
compassion at the beginning of this logic.
This is rarely
stopped.
Who is this
Avalokiteshvara?
I appoint for [something] they do
n't like. They look like how you're in love with
someone.
This is the stable gaze of a person in love. Unlock
means down. Lucas,
look,
Mr. looking at
love. And
if you write it incorrectly, it means [something] is a
typical bag and
some kind of habit. He called it Mr.
baggy eyes up to 100, something like this.
Cloth eyes, such [ __ ], looks at
all the suffering things.  Cooling
creatures in the universe and he is in them in all
lovers and a beautiful name, he
says great,
he
will not bow with diligence, he
bows to compassion as such and this is
amazing and
necessary because who should
wear comments, why is he chasing
emotions, they are a person,
there is a precedent,
Chandra Gerti did the same, the most
famous
book about emptiness, we do not consider Ari Nagarjuna
androgens, also at the beginning of the
book, step on the walls, Putin
also bows to compassion,
that is, he simply
follows, equally a precedent, us, someone before
did something strange,
just do what, than such heaviness, he
bows to emotions, he
bows to the energy that makes a
person Boris yours and will not be a cell phone,
not Boris himself, then this is cool,
why do I have this picture,
which is now the next one,
no, before this is necessary, here she is on the bed
singing and
money too, Jade sings praises,
she makes relationships praise if you
think in this, every great song
has an object that you sing about, you always
go about what such a king example Vova or
kill or  What do you want about
cars, girls,
some pleasant things,
we wish for, and when you sing, there's always something to
add about all this
praise. They're
always about worshiping something beautiful,
red, so I chose this picture.
When you
sing passionately, it's always about
something.
Now that we've completed
the vision, this
worship of a great country. By the way, what's the
difference between a country in great
compassion? This is another big topic. The
distant, great suffering. Yes, we'll
talk again for an hour. Let's apply these and
that professional wrench. We're
talking about 7, 7 points. Oh, there was the first
main idea. We had it before. What else?
I'll
help you with experiments. What am I
saying? I haven't talked about this yet. This is the
next picture.
They're sitting in this. It's not visible, but they're on the
first two
steps of the stairs. What will happen?
What was the first
two?
This is
motivation, and
lilacs and motivation. The lower motivation is to
get your own,
protect your ass from, and the argument of the lower
worlds. The
middle motivation is
now we're on someone's mouse, noise, on the second,
protect and
achieve enlightenment, and
at least try.
development of
anxiety about what
happens to you after your
death
if you want any success in
any
Rome then at least
start thinking about what will happen to you
after death we will all come to this
we will face no
one knows who will be the first of us to
leave this life and it is
strange irony of fate that even the
younger ones often leave first and
some old men
continue to remain in this world and even
Teslas they tore up get them you don't know
who will
get out of here
first I am now
visibility the first goal of Rome is the
father of what will happen after
your death and it takes many years of
training to actually begin to
worry about this or if you are
lucky then your mother will die and then you
will understand it and the
next they say next cow in
line for
slaughter and new to the slaughterhouse suddenly
wakes up about
this is the line and they all move towards
death and I am next 2 in line at
these
genetically
they made
50 thousand years the most cooperative
stupid cows
my Lamo Henry initiative
he is a master of ambushes Kishin and
He is the one in the
plant and he selected the best seeds
to sow next year
this is what we have been doing with
dogs for 50 thousand years we take the
most cooperating wolf with us
and the calm one and we
select him then from this
offspring the same thing is the same thing
docile and that's
who does not study you Rome is not just this
submissive
next in line
your grandmother died before and your mother
died before
api you will die but the next in line is not
at least understand that in the next 2 in
line
if you can understand that even if you
if you return as a person it will still be
more than me the same thing
suffering
when you are young it is not so terrible
when you are at my age then it is
not this already
very depressive oh my fingers
stopped working and my hand
stopped working and I can't walk anymore
oh I can't walk the dog there and
but I can't do this and that
I want to live longer but I can't anymore
and don't bother it doesn't matter how well you
take care of the car or hotel it doesn't matter
she
You can't start the 7 points to the river
without understanding the first ones
so that the next ones are a cow in line, even
if it's
your turn yet,
it will still come and you will start your throat will be
cut, you will start losing your
parts, well,
not there, two fingers no longer work, well, what
about these others, but they still
work, well, in general, and they too,
they just everything gradually
begins to fall apart if you begin to
have this understanding, then you will
come to the six other parts of this,
look, these two parts are like the same ones
in the laurel, therefore, no need to
talk about this, I spent ten years
explaining this to you
if you don't remember,
go and look at the notes, I
taught this for 10 years, we already finished that part,
I will again, I will not
repeat it to you, maybe the second generation will
do this about the goal for your students,
well, you did
part 2,
good 7, what was it, this
lodging, this is the desire to develop
bodhichitta,
he says 2 parts,
2 hours,
8 steps,
Jenga, this is to develop, will cure, it has two
parts, here we
are going on an amazing journey,
you are so lucky, you survived and your part did
not fall apart when  We were driving here,
there are people who didn't get here and they are
already
buried, for example, in the new one, they sing together,
back buried in,
you reached the part where we talk about the
two parts of bodhichitta,
windows nt
cufflinks
[music],
these are quite complex words,
meaning a real thing, at
the end of May, he notices something that is not real and
genuine.
I
learned my Siberian language not from a book from my
lama,
teaching that I was his slave, I was his
driver, we couldn't go anywhere without
me. I remember how I learned this. We were in
some
kind of places, and he always stopped halfway to Washington, he needed 21 cups of Tibetan tea, a name a day to kill, and he stopped and ordered hot tea, and they brought this artificial thing, this is cream, this is cream, all the way, and that's how I learned this word. The second type of breach is this is
artificial cream, and
dachshunds are like
vegetable oil,
dirty water, and he
told me, let them not give me a band, I
don't want it as a load, and
if he saw something that
upset him, he
forgot English,
but we don't sell real cream.
I  I'll pay you more, she's good,
that is, there is a
difference, which is like this
artificial cream,
let's call it an
artificial environment, cream,
that is, they were, the account can be divided into
real and
artificial, it
means people than personality, this is waving at what
you practice for other
stages of lodging,
you are trying to achieve cheerfulness because
you cannot stand the suffering
that is now in this world and it is very
difficult, especially this week, what
happened is incredible to see and my
wife simply cannot even sleep, this at
three o'clock in the morning she gets up and goes out and
sits, this is just a terrible thing and
sometimes makes you even forget about
two men, how many years we spent
studying two husbands in the kitchen, 10 years we have been
studying that when you come to the kitchen,
this
husband of yours yells at you, then it is from your
seeds, probably, that's why he
yells at you and there is no husband who, from his
own side, yells at you, this is the
meaning of
emptiness, forget these cosmic
black holes,
this means that the person who
[music]
violence is seasoned to you, he does not
exist on his own and the person does not
exist on his own, he is from you
Emptiness is happening, it's not some kind of
philosophical thing, it means people who
offend you, and not just come from you and
only from you, and you can't blame them,
they are because what produces comes from
you, it's a very difficult thing
to perceive, you can't tell everyone this,
some you just endure,
the teacher forbade you to say this, boil the sky, he
tells me only
those can become
spiritual, spiritually high marker,
it has
nothing to do with your grades,
college diploma,
some kind of law graduated only those who have a
huge,
big, kind heart, there is
such a separate word for these
people, scriptures,
high spiritual ability,
you can teach them, it will really be read
in the beginning,
you can teach them real, it will be read
not an
artificial cast, but real, that is,
this is a real perception of emptiness
when someone
kills your people, it's real, without
blaming such and such other people or
equal or rulers that he is
crazy, he has gone mad, he
may be like this, but he happens like this
from you,
real were read real cream
real come from you there is
no leader, no army,
no politician
who which you can hear about or
experience for yourself which would not be the
producers of you they all come
from you
they are today this week I was
offered to appear on television I don't have anything to
say to you either
and
I thought that I want to tell about the shelf you
know that someone
hits you with a stick and you take a
gun and shoot at the shelf and friends
I'll ask what are you doing why are you shooting at the shelf she
hit me this is not thirst and gave
the guy who was holding the stick not the shelf
shooting at this guy
no but if you start shooting at the
guy holding it
then this is anger it's not like Ukrainians
Russians there Armenians or who else
we are there I don't know should hate
this week they are just a stick and they are
held by anger
egoism
that is the disease that we all
suffer from if you want to
attack someone then you attack this disease this is
egoism and we
all have it who are here in their own head
and this is in flight
that is Buddhist philosophy we say
that there is no one who attacks you
regardless of you stop shooting at the
shelf
run hunt for the one who holds this  stick
and this is not this indecisive anger
will come up with what
screams power in the kitchen at me because
you were lying on it on someone else
last week that is, there used to be
enough
spiritually intelligent people who could
really teach the reason in the beginning but
they
came to us we are the best we
will give them artificial cream
better we give them easy cheats in the beginning
let but only
trainees in fact later he says here
in earlier days
either they died or they
turned out to be this idea
they
taught people to really be teach in the beginning
now they teach
now they
if you
teach people to really be a teacher
too early they may not understand they
may understand incorrectly and go down the
wrong path and your husband
means
calm down and don't
shout
and if from let you can just kill
can
you
don't teach them a
real future teach them
almost artificial cream in the beginning of these
people
this is the story of Mr. Elephant elephant
skin
this guy has a T
-shirt with a photo of Slanov
this is the story I
teach 8 these guys leaving food said
he his name is Mr. Elephant skin I am very
proud that I am using the database from
Brady I think that I  The first one
discovered that story, probably his 1st
personnel officer heard, you will hear this in
modern times, we have
seven minutes, I can search or
I'll start and then tomorrow we will finish
well, the
author of this comment rings
1689 was born in the greatest master of
the world, of course, he is naturally he is the
best person who can explain
this,
between what is dark to show these
texts, you need to one day
thank him for this and
also John, go through
protection from diarrhea, which
he ran into
once I
fit and gave a lecture
small, we keep 25
years
refugees do you know how many times he had
diarrhea to get here, that's
why I value John Brady so much and
praise him so much when in teaching
someone for free
you must evaluate which
student to deal with and
adapt your teaching to his needs,
that is, do not eat recklessly with everyone the
same, start with compassion and with a
kind heart, not and children, a finally
kind heart of a personnel officer is emptiness
immediately  Not with everyone,
try to
understand
this person's strategy. We'll
start with this. Then, in six months,
maybe we'll move on to more complex
things. So, set a bar for this
person. Be skillful.
Think about the effect
your teaching will have on the game. A person may be too much to
teach him now. That the
enemy is in his own mind.
That it's not another person. Urgently, flint in his
own mind. Narita. Are they ready to
hear this in force? And people are ready. You
just need to evaluate very carefully. And in
ancient times, in India, an elephant died and
Garena sings and
wolves began to eat the insides. They ate
all the guts.
They
began to eat Alize. There, inside, in
the frame,
Ron, what is it called when the ribs are still
there. The
rib cage. That is, it's a
cage with two skeletons. It
still remained intact.
That is, they are meat and the middle. And wine.
Ribs and skin. They still
remained there. Well, the meat was no longer there. That is,
the height was still outside. Not
touched in rhythm. And one Buddhist. Whether the tractor
said it would be cool for renunciation.
Go inside this rib cage and
do meditation there.
It will be real.  Yogis are cool, they
'll sit on these flies and all these
worms. This is because it will develop
your renunciation. Because we all have this.
This idea came to me. I'll climb in and start
meditating inside the
elephant's chest. I climbed in there and started meditating there.
Top
Man, I'm not in the void, that's
where
America is.  American youth
will go looking for a dead elephant. I tried something
similar.
I can tell you that at home,
when a mindmap is
more practical, I
tried it in a cave. I almost killed it, and there was a
rattlesnake,
some kind of
ran tool and other insects, and
I
had a
huge number of prize
parasites remaining in my head. That is, do
n't
go to such feats. A grimace. What you won't
find. I drank. She's here. And
others really started calling him. The
master of the
course on
Acharya.
Something about an elephant.
Apple. Karma. Raja. Invite.
Connection. Invite you to become the
most important. Break the country.
Maybe my. Remember. Minutes more. Maybe
we'll finish about this. Miles of Mr.
elephant skin.
Since Mr. received this
deep experience inside her, I will
focus on letting go. I just
trained the king. Let them
already understand where this is going.
He didn't judge
her. He didn't evaluate the
king's capabilities correctly. He
simply was inspired by his personal
experience of
emptiness, and so he decided what kind of
training he needed. By the way, at first, the final
place. He should have started with
artificial cream, and this is  kind
heart and he went straight to the
main
final absolute
he says this guy has nothing
monson to demonstrate remember
about the same volumes
straight
he will not get to me practically he has
some kind of theory not revealed sec this is
something like some kind of philosophical
reasoning
it's just a constructor
mentally does not show me anything concrete
they practically
torment me he is just this emptiness it
all the time returns to this strange of
this thing and
judging by the appearance of this person there
can not provide anything practical
I think
that he is a nist
who was carried away by some kind of nihilism this is
what in those days
were Janis you monks
scientists who said that nothing is
real everything is unreal
by the way Janis these are very wonderful
people incredibly wonderful very kind
very knowledgeable
wonderful people they still exist
today
but the king is like this
and this is not a Buddhist he is some kind of
extreme look to me trying to have an
epileptic student does not exist
he is fake he is not who
positions himself as a Buddhist
he thinks that this means that nothing
exists
he is the
same shoes to guess wrong for everyone
if I him  I will make
my people,
for whom I am not, a national master teacher, in accordance
with my kingdom,
they will ignore 10 good deeds, yes,
if virtues are there, they will go
straight into the void, and they will be more
attractive to those who do not need to defend
life,
to defend honest people from it, all this, all this,
ancient morality, and
this will be a disaster, and
he has now thus
proven that he is not a darma
teacher, a darma king, and then he
cut off his head, he
executed this mister,
already an elephant, and then he took another elephant,
another teacher,
he said,
I have already ordered my desire for material
possessions, and
since you are still mister king, you
still have not overcome
this attachment, but I cannot
be national, I cannot
be a national master in a
kingdom where the king has not yet overcome this,
and he began to teach the king in this way, from the point of
view
that if you concentrate too much on
your material things that you
own, then you simply will not have time
for spiritual meditation, others are
constantly just if they drive around the
workshop,
I like tests, I don’t like his
children, but if I already have a car
that I can use  She works
but I don't want him there I don't want to have
some extra thing that my my
time will pull out from me
I like them
if I haven't had a car yet
probably bought a Tesla
but I already have one that I
need to take care of and that's enough for me
shaft belts
back 2 teacher
0 started to
deal with him in full problems sour
started with easy things
too much heap they bought a lot of
things
just a couple of butterflies that's enough and
then after months months
then he taught him emptiness
[music]
gradually simplicity letters article failed
enjoy the old things that
you have
enjoy old jeans they are softer
they are not that expensive for a reason it's
cool to wear I have some like that
they are very comfortable soft
enjoy the old things that
you already have and don't look at the new ones
until you throw out the old ones
what he started with that and
gradually him right according to the article
and the
king saw emptiness directly because
he came there
because
his Pavel gradually there and
then the king saw according to the term after that
auch I
executed Rio the one who  I saw emptiness
directly, a huge mistake, a step by
he
did a lot of cleansing, a lot of
remorse and
this is Mr.
Pa0 skin, he was capable of it,
he came to
this king's dream
because I want, even though he was killed, but he
was Ari, then he specially visited the
dream and two kings,
if you
yourself, if you really
regret that you executed me,
killed me, then let someone draw, write,
draw my picture so that
you will remember me and that
people and the king will remember me, he, he, he
himself, do when he woke up,
drew his portrait and
he
continued to lament, you regret
in front of
other people what he did before he
received the
appropriate signs that everything was cleared and
now here is another one of the goals,
if you think
about them, both teachers
saw emptiness, but the
bridge is the difference in the levels of
problems of the tour, which, when the
first teacher was very impatient
to teach this emptiness, he did not respect the
student's abilities, his level, about his, not
him, not an executioner, was Kuman just wanted
to teach him something very
attractive and this is very  Okay, a
moralist of history has created many problems for everyone.
If you have a choice to teach
absolutely, will teach Abu more often
absolutely deduction or
artificial cream wants to distinguish between
artificial cream, then check
your students first.
Perhaps you need to start with the fact that, well,
let's develop the good news. RC,
no, that's it. Your country also has
children and wives and parents. They are also
freaks when Tanya is also human.
They all make mistakes. They all enter into this.
My father, at 17, went to war. He
killed people. In his entire life, he
deviated from his aim
when you hit a person. You would never be
able to
heal from this. In your entire life,
free yourself.
In fact, you will suffer greatly.
These soldiers should
be taught and
that what you think is cool is
killing someone. This is what you
think is cool. A
consequence of the
veterans' community.
American veterans come not so much pain from what
they saw there. They are very strong. They are
terribly broken inside. They
suffer greatly inside. This is
their experience and he sees that
they come from you. Don't say this.
Maybe it is this.  It's just not the
right time yet, the wrong time, just
a little compassion for these people,
please,
Samokisha,
brought this
story a while ago,
the teacher and
the word skin
in the land of snows, and he
messages
Japanese food,
then a hint at the final prayer, mistakes,
remember, so as not to
harm anyone with your
teaching and explanations.